<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Arnob's Odyssey</title><link>https://example.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Arnob's Odyssey</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello Friend</title><link>https://example.com/posts/hello/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/posts/hello/</guid><description>Hello and welcome to my portfolio website! My name is Arnob, and I am a software engineer with a passion for creating efficient and effective solutions to complex problems. With expertise in Java, SpringBoot, Microservices, REST, and Kafka, I strive to stay at the forefront of emerging technologies and deliver exceptional results for every project I undertake.
But it&amp;rsquo;s not all work and no play for me! In addition to my technical skills, I bring a good sense of humor to the table and love to inject some levity into even the most challenging projects.</description><content>&lt;p>Hello and welcome to my portfolio website! My name is Arnob, and I am a software engineer with a passion for creating efficient and effective solutions to complex problems. With expertise in Java, SpringBoot, Microservices, REST, and Kafka, I strive to stay at the forefront of emerging technologies and deliver exceptional results for every project I undertake.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But it&amp;rsquo;s not all work and no play for me! In addition to my technical skills, I bring a good sense of humor to the table and love to inject some levity into even the most challenging projects. When I&amp;rsquo;m not coding or brainstorming solutions, you can usually find me curled up with a good movie. I am an avid movie buff and believe that storytelling is one of the most powerful tools we have at our disposal.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I invite you to take a look around my portfolio and see some of the projects I&amp;rsquo;ve been fortunate enough to work on. From simple applications to complex systems, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the opportunity to work on a wide range of projects, each of which has taught me something new and valuable.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thank you for visiting my site, and I look forward to connecting with you soon!&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>